Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - S
        - Soul To The Rhythm - One on one love; Elevate your mind (Feel it), 1995; SR-30642; Soul To The Rhythm; Kingsize; Godwin; Grisel A. (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30643. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DIG P6; A-side Matrix # DIG P6 A
        - Soul To The Rhythm - One on one love; Elevate your mind (Feel it), 1995; SR-30643; Soul To The Rhythm; Kingsize; Godwin; Grisel A. (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30642. 2 copies.
        - Soulchild, Musiq - Buddy, 2006; SR-30644; Soulchild, Musiq (Box 440)
          Catalog # PR 302432; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302432A-1 RJ STERLING
        - Soulchild, Musiq - Forthenight (Remix); Whoknows, 2004; SR-30645; Soulchild, Musiq; Comp (Box 440)
          Catalog # DEFR 16026-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16026-1A RJ STERLING
        - Soulchild, Musiq - Soulstar, 2003; SR-30646; Soulchild, Musiq; Riddick, Carol; Cee-Lo; AAries; Kindred The Family Soul; Bilal (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30647. 2 copies.
          Catalog # B0001616-01; A-side Matrix # B0001616-01-LP1A
        - Soulchild, Musiq - Soulstar, 2003; SR-30647; Soulchild, Musiq; Riddick, Carol; Cee-Lo; AAries; Kindred The Family Soul; Bilal (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30646. 2 copies.
        - Soulchild, Musiq - Aijuswanaseing (disc one), 2000; SR-30648; Soulchild, Musiq; Aaries (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30649. Double album.
          Catalog # 314-548 289-1; A-side Matrix # 314-548-290-1A RJ STERLING X1
        - Soulchild, Musiq - Aijuswanaseing (disc two), 2000; SR-30649; Soulchild, Musiq; Aaries (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30648. Double album.
          Catalog # 314-548 289-1; A-side Matrix # 314-548-290-1C RJ STERLING X1
        - Soultry - Cash money, 1995; SR-30650; Soultry (Box 440)
          Catalog # 374631306-1; A-side Matrix # 374631306-1-A K2 1-1
        - Soultry - Cash money, 1995; SR-30651; Soultry (Box 440)
          Catalog # 374631312-1; A-side Matrix # 37463-1312-1A-SP1
        - Soultry - Cash money, 1995; SR-30652; Soultry (Box 440)
        - Sound Authority - On the uprise; Get it up, 1990; SR-30653; Sound Authority; MC Izzy-Iz (Box 440)
          Catalog # VR-1247; A-side Matrix # VR-1247-A FULLERSOUND MF
        - Sound Doctor - Tonight's just right, 1982; SR-30654; Sound Doctor (Box 440)
          Catalog # 4W9 2709; A-side Matrix # 4W9-02709-AS-2A COLUMBIA NY
        - Sound On Sound Productions - Tribute to the greatesss, 1980; SR-30655; Sound On Sound Productions (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30656. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PT-7004; A-side Matrix # PT-7004-A FW HP
          Reflection Records
        - Sound On Sound Productions - Tribute to the greatesss, 1980; SR-30656; Sound On Sound Productions (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30655. 2 copies.
        - Space Travelers - Sound pollution, 2008; SR-30657; Space Travelers (Box 440)
          Catalog # SND-711; A-side Matrix # SND-711-A SAE MASTERING 5151.1
          Gonervill Records
        - Sound Troupe - Can you really see me, 1982; SR-30658; Sound Troupe (Box 440)
          Catalog # S-12348; A-side Matrix # S-12348-1 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr.
          Sam Records
        - Sounds of Blackness - Hold on (Change is comin'), 1997; SR-30659; Sounds of Blackness (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30660. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PSPRO 00544; A-side Matrix # PSPRO 00544 A AG
        - Sounds of Blackness - Hold on (Change is comin'), 1997; SR-30660; Sounds of Blackness (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30659. 2 copies.
        - Sounds of Blackness - I'm going all the way, 1994; SR-30661; Sounds of Blackness (Box 440)
          Catalog # 31458 8373 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 8373 1A SP1
        - Sounds of Blackness - The pressure (Pt. 1) (disc one), 1991; SR-30662; Sounds of Blackness; Prof T. (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30663. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 28968 1202 1; A-side Matrix # 28968-1202-E-E2 SP1-1 #08762
        - Sounds of Blackness - The pressure (Pt. 1) (disc two), 1991; SR-30663; Sounds of Blackness; Prof T. (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30662. 2 copies.
        - Source - You got the love, 1996; SR-30664; Source; Candi Staton (Box 440)
          Catalog # 12 REACT 89; A-side Matrix # 12 REACT 89-B1
        - Source Direct - Capital D; Enemy lines, 1997; SR-30665; Source Direct (Box 440)
          Catalog # QEDTDJ5; A-side Matrix # QEDT 5 AA-2-1-1
          Science
        - Source Direct - Mind weaver, 1998; SR-30666; Source Direct (Box 440)
          Catalog # QEDLPDX 3; A-side Matrix # QEDLPDX 3 A-1-1-
        - Source Direct - Exorcise the demons (disc one), 1999; SR-30667; Source Direct (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30668; SR-30669. Triple album.
          Catalog # QEDLP 3; A-side Matrix # QEDLP 003 A-01-01-01-1
        - Source Direct - Exorcise the demons (disc two), 1999; SR-30668; Source Direct (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30667; SR-30669. Triple album.
          Catalog # QEDLP 3; A-side Matrix # QEDLP 003 C-01-01-01-1
        - Source Direct - Exorcise the demons (disc three), 1999; SR-30669; Source Direct (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30668; SR-30667. Triple album.
          Catalog # QEDLP 3; A-side Matrix # QEDLP 003 E-01-01-01-1
        - Source Direct - Technical warfare, 1999; SR-30670; Source Direct (Box 440)
          Catalog # QEDLPDY 3; A-side Matrix # QEDLPDY 3 A-1-1- Stu
        - Source Of Labor - Overstandings; Whatever, 1997; SR-30671; Source Of Labor; Beyond Reality; Kollars, Nikol; Loud, Felicia (Box 440)
          Catalog # jmgv1; A-side Matrix # S 35314 RE2
          Jasiri Media Group
        - South Bronx - The big throwdown, 1981; SR-30672; South Bronx (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30673. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # D-219; A-side Matrix # D-219 A-2-1-11 PRC MASTERDISK HW
          Brunswick
        - South Bronx - The big throwdown, 1981; SR-30673; South Bronx (Box 440)
          In same jacket as # SR-30672. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - South Central Cartel - N gatz we truss, 1994; SR-30674; South Central Cartel; Big Mike; 3-2; Spice 1; 2Pac; Ice-T; Mc Eiht (Box 440)
          Catalog # O 57294; A-side Matrix # AL-57294-1A MASTERDISK
        - South Central Cartel - Gang stories, 1994; SR-30675; South Central Cartel; Big Mike; 3-2 (Box 440)
          Catalog # 42 77367; A-side Matrix # XSS-77367-A-1B
        - South Click - Rebel slave; Breakout, 1998; SR-30676; South Click (Box 440)
          Catalog # PW PROMO 321; A-side Matrix # PW PROMO-321-1A S 36349 TR3121 B S
          Power Records
          Norcross, Georgia
        - South Click - Rebel slave; Breakout, 1998; SR-30677; South Click (Box 440)
        - South Click - Rebel slave; Breakout, 1998; SR-30678; South Click (Box 441)
        - South East Section - Thought I'd forget (To be real), 1996; SR-30679; South East Section (Box 441)
          Catalog # NTR 008; A-side Matrix # NTR-008-A1
          Nightown Records
        - South East Section - Thought I'd forget (To be real), 1996; SR-30680; South East Section (Box 441)
        - South Park Mexican - You know my name, 2000; SR-30681; South Park Mexican (Box 441)
          Catalog # 012 158 350-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR- 20297 1 A RE1 012 158 350-1 A
        - Southern Playas - Dirty south bass track; Dickey ride, 1996; SR-30683; Southern Playas; L.A. Sno; Kidd Money (Box 441)
          Catalog # CRAB 15589-1; A-side Matrix # CRAB-15539-1-A1 Kr
          Critique
        - Southernaire Allstars - I believe, 2001; SR-30684; Southernaire Allstars; Static (Box 441)
          Catalog # 7087 6 15740 1 2; A-side Matrix # 70876-15740-1-2 A
          Blackground Entertainment
        - Southroad Connection - We came to funk you out, 1980; SR-30685; Southroad Connection (Box 441)
          Catalog # SP-201; A-side Matrix # SP-1-201-Z1
          United Artists Records
        - Southside Movement - Southside Movement, 1973; SR-30682; Southside Movement (Box 441)
          Catalog # WDS 695; A-side Matrix # WDS-695-A-1A
          Wand
        - Southside Reverb - Go get on it, 1997; SR-30686; Southside Reverb (Box 441)
          Catalog # ESU 1969; A-side Matrix # ESU-1969-1 B
          ESP-SUN Records
        - Southsyde B.O.I.Z. - Get ready, here it comes (It’s the choo-choo), 1996; SR-30687; Southsyde B.O.I.Z. (Box 441)
          Catalog # LFDP-4159; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4159-SA-SP1 A FULLERSOUND PF
          Laface Records
        - Soweto - African warrior, 1978; SR-30688; Soweto (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30689. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DK 4608; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-34985-1 ATLANTIC STUDIOS DK
        - Soweto - African warrior, 1978; SR-30689; Soweto (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30688. 2 copies.
        - Soyini, Ayana - The khamouflage project, 2000; SR-30690; Soyini, Ayana (Box 441)
          Catalog # TKP0001; A-side Matrix # TKP-0001 A MD
          Goldeneyes Entertainment
        - S.P. 1200 - Pump it; To the three, 1997; SR-30691; S.P. 1200 (Box 441)
          Catalog # AB035; A-side Matrix # AB-0035A S-34636
          Aqua Boogie Records
        - SP Funk - O lado b do hip hop, 2001; SR-30692; SP Funk; Thaide (Box 441)
          Catalog # 1003-53; A-side Matrix # 1003-52 A SP FUNK-A
          Eu Q Fiz Discos
        - SP Funk - Lado "B"' do hip hop, 2001; SR-30693; SP Funk; Kamau; Max B.O.; Suave (Box 441)
          Catalog # 1002-72; A-side Matrix # 1002-72 A SP FUNK-A
        - Space - Carry on, turn me on; Tango in space, 1977; SR-30694; Space (Box 441)
          Catalog # UA-DW1024; A-side Matrix # UAST-18724-D
        - Space - My love is music, 1979; SR-30695; Space (Box 441)
          Catalog # NBD 20156 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20156-AS P1
        - Space - Magic fly, 1977; SR-30696; Space (Box 441)
          Catalog # UA-LA780-G; A-side Matrix # UA-LA 780-1
        - Space - Magic fly, 1977; SR-30697; Space (Box 441)
          Catalog # NSPL 28232; A-side Matrix # NSPL 28232 A-1DMB
          Pye International
        - Space Bats - Mission one, 1998; SR-30698; Space Bats (Box 441)
          Catalog # 12 gotwax 001; A-side Matrix # 12 gotwax-001-A1
          Gotcha!
        - Space Brothers - Forgiven (I feel your love), 1997; SR-30699; Space Brothers (Box 441)
          Catalog # FESX 36; A-side Matrix # BRO DJ 1 A1 = FESX 36 A1
          Manifesto
        - Space Family Unit - Final, 1995; SR-30700; Space Family Unit; Duverney, Ondrea (Box 441)
          Catalog # ABC-003; A-side Matrix # ABC-003-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 13360
          Alphabet Music
        - Space Invaders - The phoenix E.P., 1997; SR-30701; Space Invaders (Box 441)
          Catalog # Swell 003; A-side Matrix # SWELL-03-A L-46281
          Swell Records
          Scottsdale, Arizona
        - Space Raiders - Glam raid, 1998; SR-30702; Space Raiders (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30703. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # skint 32; A-side Matrix # SKINT+32+AA GRAZ- THE EXCHANGE
        - Space Raiders - Glam raid, 1998; SR-30703; Space Raiders (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30702. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Spain - The blue moods of Spain, 1995; SR-30704; Spain (Box 441)
          Catalog # 72910; A-side Matrix # DFI 95-10 SPAIN LP PROMO 72910
          Restless Records
          El Segundo, California
        - Spandau Ballet - Lifeline, 1982; SR-30705; Spandau Ballet (Box 441)
          Catalog # CHS 12 2642; A-side Matrix # CHS 122642 A//1 420 P 1 1 1 5
          Chrysalis
        - Spandau Ballet - Gold (Special extended remix), 1983; SR-30706; Spandau Ballet (Box 441)
          Catalog # 4V9 42740; A-side Matrix # 4V9-42740-AS -2 STERLING P
        - Spandau Ballet - True, 1983; SR-30707; Spandau Ballet (Box 441)
          Catalog # B6V 41403; A-side Matrix # B6V-41403-BS-2 MASTERDISK HW
        - Spandau Ballet - Chant No. 1 (I don't need this pressure on), 1981; SR-30708; Spandau Ballet (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30709. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # CDS 2528; A-side Matrix # CDS-2528-AS SM-1 SX MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
        - Spandau Ballet - Chant No. 1 (I don't need this pressure on), 1981; SR-30709; Spandau Ballet (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30708. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Spanish Fly - Precious, 1991; SR-30710; Spanish Fly (Box 441)
          Catalog # UR 0102; A-side Matrix # SAC UR-102A C1 DIS SIDE G1 (T) A3 We're Dope Face It
          Upstairs Records
          San Jose, California
        - Spanky II Music - Dj Drum copy, 2000; SR-30711; Spanky II Music (Box 441)
          Catalog # Scorp 1024; A-side Matrix # L-13183M-A
          Scorp
        - Spark 950 - United we slam, 1993; SR-30712; Spark 950; Timbo King (Box 441)
          Catalog # SBDJ 75429-1; A-side Matrix # SBAB-75429-1-A S-29055
          Street Life Records
        - Spark 950 - United we slam, 1993; SR-30713; Spark 950; Timbo King (Box 441)
        - Sparkle - Time to move on, 1998; SR-30714; Sparkle (Box 441)
          Catalog # INT8P 6460; A-side Matrix # INT8P-6460-A
        - Sparkle - Love by starlight, 1988; SR-30715; Sparkle (Box 441)
          Catalog # UN 3002; A-side Matrix # UN-3002-A 1-1 MASTERED BY TRUTONE PA 485
          Universe Records
        - Sparks - Pretending to be drunk, 1984; SR-30716; Sparks (Box 441)
          Catalog # PR 644; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-46766-1
        - Sparks - Progress, 1984; SR-30717; Sparks (Box 441)
          Catalog # DMD 753; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-46492-46494-2 1-1
        - Sparks - Cool places, 1983; SR-30718; Sparks; Wiedlin, Jane (Box 441)
          Catalog # DMD 613; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-44365-1 1-1
        - Sparks, Melvin - Sparks!, 1970; SR-30719; Sparks, Melvin (Box 441)
          Catalog # PR 10001; A-side Matrix # PRST 10001-A RE 1
        - Sparks, Melvin - Melvin sparks '75, 1975; SR-30720; Sparks, Melvin; Scott, Jimmy (Box 441)
          Catalog # W-204; A-side Matrix # M-204-AS-1B
          20th Century Records
        - Sparks, Melvin - Akilah!, 1972; SR-30721; Sparks, Melvin (Box 441)
          Catalog # PR-10039; A-side Matrix # PRST-10039-A STERLING
        - Sparky D - Throwdown, 1987; SR-30722; Sparky D (Box 441)
          Catalog # BB-10-77; A-side Matrix # BB-10-77-A DCHARLES
          B-Boy Records
        - Sparky D - Sparky's turn (Roxanne you're through), 1985; SR-30723; Sparky D (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30724. 2 copies.
          Catalog # N 1245; A-side Matrix # NI 1245 AS
          NIA Records
        - Sparky D - Sparky's turn (Roxanne you're through), 1985; SR-30724; Sparky D (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30723. 2 copies.
        - Sparky D - She's so def; He's my dj, 1985; SR-30725; Sparky D; Red Alert (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30726. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NI 1250-1; A-side Matrix # NI-1250-A-1
        - Sparky D - She's so def; He's my dj, 1985; SR-30726; Sparky D; Red Alert (Box 441)
          In same jacket as # SR-30725. 2 copies.
        - Sparky D - The battle, 1985; SR-30727; Sparky D; Playgirls (Box 441)
          Catalog # NI 1246; A-side Matrix # NI-1246-A PRESSED AT SOUND MAKERS N.J.
        - Sparky Lightbourne - Sparky's secret, 1997; SR-30728; Sparky Lightbourne (Box 441)
          Catalog # skint 29; A-side Matrix # SKINT 29 B1 OR WHEN THE FINGER POINTS TO THE MOON THE IDIOT LOOKS AT THE FINGER
        - Sparque - Music turns me on, 1982; SR-30729; Sparque (Box 441)
          Catalog # WES 22141; A-side Matrix # WES-22141-B-RE-70501-INST
          West End Records
        - Mighty Sparrow - Doctor Bird, 1988; SR-30730; Mighty Sparrow; Sparrow (Box 441)
          Catalog # CRM&M 0018; A-side Matrix # CRMM0018-A
        - Sparrooowww - Sparrow vs the rest, 1976; SR-30731; Sparrooowww; Sparrow (Box 441)
          Catalog # SP-1976; A-side Matrix # SP-1976-S1
          Tysott
          Canada
        - Mighty Sparrow - All in the game, 1989; SR-30732; Mighty Sparrow; Sparrow (Box 441)
          Catalog # SCR 3868; A-side Matrix # SCR-3868-A RE-3 CS
        - Sparrow - Sparrow at the Hilton, 1967; SR-30733; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # NRC 8070; A-side Matrix # NRC 8070 A
          Ra
        - King Sparrow - King Sparrow's calypso carnival, 1959; SR-30734; King Sparrow; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # 920; A-side Matrix # CT 920 A
          Cook
          Stamford, Connecticut
        - Sparrow - Sparrow come back, 1962; SR-30735; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # LPB-3006; A-side Matrix # N8 OP1112--1A
        - Sparrow - Jump for Jesse!, 1988; SR-30736; Sparrow; Rudder, David; Victory, George; Sarafina (Box 442)
          Catalog # ND 122801; A-side Matrix # ND 122801-A RE
          New Dove Productions, Inc.
        - Mighty Sparrow - The greatest, 1983; SR-30737; Mighty Sparrow; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # JAF 1006; A-side Matrix # JAF-1006-A-RE2
          Sparrow Music
          Barbados
        - Sparrow - Let the music play, 1990; SR-30738; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # 101-1; A-side Matrix # SPASM-0101-B Sparrow '90 VP-RICE
          Spasm Records
        - Sparrow - Sparrow's dance party (disc one), 1992; SR-30739; Sparrow (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-30740. Double album.
          Catalog # BLS-1015; A-side Matrix # BLS-1015-A DCHARLES
          BLS Records
          Frederiksted, St Croix, US Virgin Islands
        - Sparrow - Sparrow's dance party (disc two), 1992; SR-30740; Sparrow (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-30739. Double album.
          Catalog # BLS-1015; A-side Matrix # BLS-1015-C DCHARLES
        - Sparrow - Sparrow power, 1970; SR-30741; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # RA-2021; A-side Matrix # RA 2021 A HILLARY STERLING
          Hilary
        - Sparrow - Many moods of Sparrow, SR-30742; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # BW 1001; A-side Matrix # BW-1001-S1 AMD
          Island Series
        - Mighty Sparrow - One love one heart, 1987; SR-30743; Mighty Sparrow; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # BSR-SP-069; A-side Matrix # BSR-SP-069A
        - Sparrow - King of the world, 1984; SR-25122; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # BSR-SP-002; A-side Matrix # BSR-1-SO-002-A
        - Mighty Sparrow - Congo man, 1965; SR-13082; Mighty Sparrow; Sparrow (Box 442)
          Catalog # NLP-5050; A-side Matrix # NLP 50050-1
          National Recording Company
          Trinidad, West Indies
        - Vince Spaulding & the Mastersplits - Rock Creek Park, 1989; SR-25123; Vince Spaulding & the Mastersplits (Box 442)
          Catalog # FLY 014R; A-side Matrix # FLY 014R-A
          Flying Records
          Naples, Italy
        - Spaze-Ka-Dett - ET in america, 1982; SR-30744; Spaze-Ka-Dett (Box 442)
          Catalog # EIR-103; A-side Matrix # EIR-103-A-DJ MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
          Emerald International Records
        - Spear Of Destiny - Strangers in our town, 1987; SR-30745; Spear Of Destiny (Box 442)
          Catalog # DMD 1043; A-side Matrix # STDM-51660-1 1-1 Precision
        - Spearhead - People in tha middle, 1994; SR-30746; Spearhead (Box 442)
          Catalog # Y 7243 8 58270 1 3; A-side Matrix # Y-58270-A F-1 MASTERED BY CAPITOL Wally
        - Spears, Britney - Stronger, 2001; SR-30747; Spears, Britney; Migs, Miguel (Box 442)
          Catalog # JDAB-42862-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42862-1 A MCR-RCE
          Jive Electro
        - Spears, Britney - Key cuts from remixed, 2005; SR-30748; Spears, Britney; Madonna (Box 442)
          Catalog # 82876-74807-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-74807- A
        - Spears, Britney - I'm a slave 4 u (The remixes), 2001; SR-30749; Spears, Britney (Box 442)
          Catalog # 9252750; A-side Matrix # 9252750 P-A1 JA
        - Spears, Britney - Outrageous (Remixes), 2004; SR-30750; Spears, Britney (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-30751. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 82876-63276-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-63276-1 A RE 1
        - Spears, Britney - Outrageous (Remixes), 2004; SR-30751; Spears, Britney (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-30750. 2 copies.
        - Spears, Britney - I'm a slave 4 u (disc one), 2001; SR-30752; Spears, Britney (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-30753. Double album.
          Catalog # 9252750P; A-side Matrix # 9252750 P - A1 MA JA
        - Spears, Britney - I'm a slave 4 u (disc two), 2001; SR-30753; Spears, Britney (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-30752. Double album.
        - Spears, Britney - I'm a slave 4 u, 2001; SR-30754; Spears, Britney (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-30755. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 01241-42967-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-42967-1A
        - Spears, Britney - I'm a slave 4 u, 2001; SR-30755; Spears, Britney (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-30754. 2 copies.
        - Special AKA - Free Nelson Mandela (The special remix), 1984; SR-30756; Special AKA (Box 442)
          Catalog # 4V9 42793; A-side Matrix # 4V9-42793-A-CP1 STERLING
        - Special Ed - Neva go back; Just a killa, 1995; SR-30757; Special Ed; Bounty Killer (Box 442)
          Catalog # PRO-7433-0DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7433-0-A MASTERDISK TD
        - Special Ed - Lyrics, 1995; SR-30758; Special Ed (Box 442)
          Catalog # PRO-7446-0; A-side Matrix # PRO-7446-0-A RE 1-1 MASTERDISK TD
        - Special Forces - Stroke it, 1982; SR-30759; Special Forces (Box 442)
          Catalog # SG 381 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-381-A- -1 MASTERING BY FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK HERbIE Jr
        - Special Generation - Love me just for me, 1990; SR-30760; Special Generation (Box 442)
          Catalog # V-15607; A-side Matrix # V-1-15607-Z2
        - Special K - Twist, 2002; SR-30761; Special K (Box 442)
          Catalog # URBTAKE 33; A-side Matrix # URBTAKE 33-A TRANSITION
          Urban Takeover
        - Special K - Poka dot bikini, 1989; SR-30762; Special K (Box 442)
          Catalog # DJ 523; A-side Matrix # MIC-523 A-1A A1
          Micmac Records, Inc.
          Bayville, New Jersey
        - Special K - Poka dot bikini, 1989; SR-30763; Special K (Box 442)
          Catalog # MIC 523; A-side Matrix # MIC-523 A-1A A1
        - Special K - Special-K is good; Let's rock, 1987; SR-25124; Special K (Box 442)
          Catalog # PA 013; A-side Matrix # PA-013 A
          Public Records
        - Special Projects - Kid Loops vs. Cool Breeze, 1996; SR-25125; Special Projects; Kid Loops; Cool Breeze (Box 442)
          Catalog # FILT 012 P; A-side Matrix # FILT 012 P-A1
          Filter
        - Special-T - It's your love, 1983; SR-25126; Special-T (Box 442)
          Catalog # NP 50017; A-side Matrix # NP 50017 A 3
        - Special Tee - Everybody get up, 1988; SR-25127; Special Tee (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-25128. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # OP001; A-side Matrix # OP001-PHATT SIDE A
          Oomph Pah Records
        - Special Tee - Everybody get up, 1988; SR-25128; Special Tee (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-25127. Multiple copies.
        - Speed Knot Mobsters - In your world; Adrenaline rush, 1996; SR-25129; Speed Knot Mobsters (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-25130. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 2465; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-88253 88254-1
          Big Beat
        - Speed Knot Mobsters - In your world; Adrenaline rush, 1996; SR-25130; Speed Knot Mobsters (Box 442)
          In same jacket as # SR-25129. Different discs.
        - Speedy - Hold your bam bam, 1991; SR-25131; Speedy (Box 442)
          Catalog # WR1560; A-side Matrix # HOLD YA BAM BAM ROGER007
          Wrecker Records
        - Speedy J - A shocking hobby, 2000; SR-25132; Speedy J (Box 442)